<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="mTitles">
        <item>The Nest of Magpie</item>
        <item>Believe in yourself</item>
        <item>Defeating the Bully</item>
        <item>The Beetle Who Challenged the Elephant</item>
        <item>The Gardener and the Donkey</item>
        <item>The Man, the Boy, and the Donkey</item>
        <item>How the Turtle Saved Its Life</item>
        <item>The Deer Who Played Truant</item>
        <item>The Hungry Mouse</item>
        <item>The Shepherd’s Mistake</item>
        <item>The Cow’s Bell</item>
        <item>Jim’s Puppy</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="mfs">
        <item>
            The magpie builds the most comfortable and beautiful nests on the world. So , one day all the other birds asked him to teach them how to make really good nests. The magpie agreed.
            He said, “Firstly,take some mud and make a sort of round shape.” “oh, that’s it!” cried the thrush and he flew away. Since then the thrushes are building their nests in that way.
            Then the magpie continued, “Next, take some twigs and arrange them around the mud.” “So that’s it” exclaimed the blackbird and he left . In that way the blackbirds are building their nests even today.
            So it wnt on, every bird taking away a little piece of the knowledge but none of them remained there until the end. The magpiewent on working without looking up, but when he saw that nobody is there he got angry and flew away. He never again showed the others how to build nests.
            MORAL :It is wise to wait the end to get to know everything.
        </item>
        <item>
            Anita was a bubbly female child who grew up within the Himalayan abode of snow, within the eastern region of Nepal. Her parents were Sheppards.
            It was that point of the year when the sky was blue, sun smiled upon the village and therefore the stars in the dark never looked brighter before.
            Anita found a lot of tourists visit her village. Watching people from everywhere the planet visit her village made Anita curious. "What are these people doing here father?" asked Anita.
            Anita\'s father laughed and said, "Darling, they have all come to climb those mountains."
            Amazed at their courage, Anita said, "Really father? Is it possible to climb to the top?"
            "Of course dear," replied her father. Many people do it.
            "Someday, I will be able to climb to the highest of these majestic mountains" said Anita with a resounding streak of hope, a burning dream brewing in her eyes.
            But Life had other plans for her. Anita lost one among her legs when she was thirteen. Clouds of despair overshadowed her happy world.
            "l will never be ready to climb those mountains," cried Anita.
            Her father loved her dearly. He couldn\'t see his little girl in pain. He too was devastated. But he did not loose heart.
            One day Anita\'s father built her a peg, a wooden leg, which she could wear and walk.
            "Never say \'never\'. Start climbing the mountains," said the determined father.
            Believe in yourself Anita was beside herself with joy. She wore the wooden limb and walked, and fell. Stood up, and tried to run, and fell again.
            The entire village laughed at the daddy and daughter\'s foolishness. But nothing pulled them down. Both the father and daughter were determined to win against all odds.
            They kept practicing.
            After five years Anita made it to the highest of the mountains. And she made her father very proud of her, along with her country.
            Moral: Never let words of discouragement pull you down. Don\'t let others tell you: "you cannot roll in the hay". Always believe yourself.
        </item>
        <item>
            Makaal was an enormous, strong, bully in class. He pushed round the other boys, beat them up, ate their lunch, and made them do his homework. His endless torture was unbearable.One day the boys got together and decided to face up against Makaal."When he beats one among us, all folks will stand together to fight back," said a boy.The other said, "If he eats our lunch, we\'ll stand together to retrieve it back from him."Another one said, "I won\'t do his homework anymore. If he forces, we\'ll march to the teacher together to complain."It was decided that they will all stand together when Makaal bullies anybody of them again.When the time came, those boys stood together, as a team and showed Makaal that they weren\'t scared of him anymore. Makaal tried to push them harder. In the process, he got beaten up by all the boys.Thereafter, Makaal never bullied anybody again, as he was shown his place.
            Moral: One man cannot fight a battle. But team can. Team work helps in achieving our goals.
        </item>
        <item>
            One day a dung beetle was flying in the streets. Suddenly, it spotted a dustbin at a corner. She went to it and found some; liquor bottles. She flew near the bottles and licked the few remaining drops. Then, buzzing happily, it returned to its heap of dung.After sometime, an elephant was passing by the dung heap. It smelled the dung and moved away due to its foul smell. The beetle saw this and got angry. It was under the effect of the liquor, so she thought that the elephant was a weak animal; She went to the elephant and said, “Let\'s fight and see who Wins.” The elephant looked at the beetle, but ignored her. The beetle was overexcited and started challenging the elephant. The elephant lost his patience and crushed the bettle at once under his limbs.
            MORAL :We should not challenge a person having a high potential.
        </item>
        <item>
            A gardener used to go to the market every week in the neighbouring town along with his donkey. He was so cruel that he loaded the donkey with a lot of load that only his head could be seen.The road that led home ran through a wood. The gardener saw some branches which he considered would be useful for him. So, he started placing them on the donkey\'s back. Then they moved further and he kept a rush of canes on the back of the donkey. The gardener kept on keeping things on the animal\'s back. The sun had risen further in the sky and it became much warmer. The gardener took off his jacket and placed it on top of the load. Within no time, the donkey fell on the ground as it could not carry such heavy load. The gardener thought, “I should not have kept so much of load on his back.”
            MORAL :Hew not too high lest the chip fall in your eye.
        </item>
        <item>
            So the Man ordered his Boy to get off, and got on himself. But they hadn\'t gone far when they passed two women, one of whom said to the other: "Shame on that lazy lout to let his poor little son trudge along."Well, the Man didn\'t know what to do, but at last he took his Boy up before him on the Donkey. By this time they had come to the town, and the passers-by began to jeer and point at them. The Man stopped and asked what they were scoffing at. The men said: "Aren\'t you ashamed of yourself for overloading that poor donkey of yours and your hulking son?"The Man and Boy got off and tried to think what to do. They thought and they thought, till at last they cut down a pole, tied the donkey\'s feet to it, and raised the pole and the donkey to their shoulders. They went along amid the laughter of all who met them till they came to Market Bridge, when the Donkey, getting one of his feet loose, kicked out and caused the Boy to drop his end of the pole. In the struggle the Donkey fell over the bridge, and his fore-feet being tied together he was drowned.
            "That will teach you," said an old man who had followed them:
            "Please all, and you will please none."
        </item>
        <item>
            A Man and his son were once going with their Donkey to market. As they were walking along by its side a countryman passed them and said: "You fools, what is a Donkey for but to ride upon?"
            So the Man put the Boy on the Donkey and they went on their way. But soon they passed a group of men, one of whom said: "See that lazy youngster, he lets his father walk while he rides."
            Once a king built a pool in his palace for his young children to play in. He ordered his men to put some fish into the pond. By mistake, the men also put in a turtle.One day the princess went into the pool to play, she saw the turtle and got afraid. She ran to the king and said, “There is a demon in the pool,” Then the king ordered his men to kill the turtle. But they did not know how to kill the turtle. Then an old man said, “Why don\'t we throw him into the water from where the water flows out over the rocks into the river. He would be killed that way.” When the turtle heard this, he said, “Oh no! Please don\'t do that to me.” The men did as the old man suggested and hence, the turtle was led out. The turtle was happy as he swam back home.
            MORAL :We should act intelligently.
        </item>
        <item>
            One day a doe brought her son to a wise deer teacher. She said to the teacher, “My dear master, please teach my son tricks to save himself from danger.” The teacher agreed and started teaching the doe from the next day.
            For the first few days, he took the lessons, but as the days passed it became restless. He was interested in playing rather than learning tricks to save himself from dangers. Soon he also started missing his classes.
            One day, while playing, he stepped on to a snare and got trapped. When his mother got to know about the incident, she broke into tears. The teacher went up to her and said, “Dear sister, sorry for what happened to your son. I tried to teach him, but he was not willing to learn. ”
            MORAL :A teacher can’t do anything , if he student is not willing to learn.

        </item>
        <item>
            There lived a mouse that was hungry from many days. She could find no food at all. She looked here and there, but found no food. Hence, she grew thin. One day the mouse found a basket full of corn. There was a small hole in the basket. She went inside and began to eat the corn greedily. As she was very hungry, she went on eating and eating. Now, she had grown very fat.After the meal, the mouse tried to come out of the basket, she could not. Now, she was too fat to pass through the hole.She said, ”How shall I come out?” Just then a rat came along, and he heard the mouse. The rat said, ”Mouse, if you want to come out of the basket, you must wait till you have grown as thin were when you went in.”
            MORAL :We should bot be greedy
        </item>
        <item>
            Once upon a time, there lived a shepherd. Every morning, he used to take out his sheep to graze in the field. While his sheep would graze, he would sit and watch them grazing.
            One day, he was sitting in the field and his sheeps were grazing the field. Suddenly, he saw a wolf behind a tree. The shepherd got afraid as he thought that the wolf would harm his sheeps. He tookhis flock of sheep back home. The wolf followed the flock of sheep and did not harm them.
            One day, he was called at home. The shepherd thought that his sheeps would be safe with the wolf. I-le called the wolf and let it live in his farm and he went home.After a few days the shepherd returned back. On reaching his home he saw that the wolf had eaten up most of his sheeps. Only a few sheep were left. He took a stick and made the wolf exit from his farm. The shepherd sat in the corner and said, “lt was my fault. I am a foolish man. I trusted the my sheep.” He went inside his house and cried. Now he could not get his sheeps back again.
            MORAL :We should not trust everyone easily.
        </item>
        <item>
            Henry, the young peasant-boy, was guarding the herd of cows in the woods. Each cow had a bell around his neck and the most beautiful cow had the best bell.
            One day a stranger passed through the woods and looked the herd of cows. He went to Henry and asked to give him a bell from one of his cow. Henry agreed and took forty bucks in return. Now the cow did not have the bell. The stranger wanted to steal the cow. Then the cow went off into the woods and the stranger took it by the horns and led it away.
            Just then Henry realised that the cow was missing and he could not trace it. So, he went back home crying and narrated the story to his father. His father said: "In the same way as that thief has deceived you, so the pleasures of sin try to deceive us all. If we give in just a little it wants everything." Henry felt ashamed for having greed for money and promised not to do such a mistake ever again.
            MORAL :Make new friends but keep the old. The one is sliver, the older gold.
        </item>
        <item>
              Jim’s father gifted Jim a puppy on his tenth birthday. Jim named the puppy as Brownie. Soon , Jim and Brownie beacme fond of each other. One Day, Jim went to the river and caught a big fish. Jim got excited and Brownie started barking loudly, encouraging Jim. Jim leaned down, fighting the mighty fish , he tried to grab it and he hit his head on the side of the canoe. He fell into the water and was unable to swim. Brownie grabbed Jim’s shirt and swam to the shore. Jim woke up fealing dizzy and confused on the river bank. Brownie was licking his face and Jim smiled. Brownie had just saved his life. Then they both headed towards the home.After a long walk, Jim saw his father at home , standing by the shoreline. He was wating for jim and brownie to retrun. Jim ran up to his father and told him about the incident. Jim’s father thanked Brownie for saving his son . He Rubbed Brownie’s head effectionately. They all smiled and went inside the home
              MORAL :A best companion will always get you out of difficulties.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>